MATH TEACHER RESUME

Personal Details

Name: Michael Brown

Date of Birth: 29/10/1998

Address: Chicago City

• Phone: (574)838 3937

• Email: Brown29Michael@gmail.com

Summary

Michael Brown is an experienced Math Teacher with a passion for helping students understand and apply mathematical concepts. He has a proven track record of designing and delivering creative and effective lesson plans that engage students and ensure success. He possesses excellent communication and interpersonal skills and is an enthusiastic team player.

Work Experience

- Math Teacher Brooklyn Latin School, Brooklyn New York 2022-2024 – Present
 - Designing and delivering effective lesson plans for students of all levels.
 - Monitoring student performance and providing feedback.
 - Working with other teachers to develop new teaching methods.
- Math Tutor, Townsend Harris High School New York City -2019 – 2022
 - Providing individual and small group tutoring for Math students.
 - Developing lesson plans to help students improve their understanding of Math concepts.
 - Assisting students with Math homework.

Education

- Bachelor of Education in Mathematics CUNY Queens College New York – 2014 – 2017
- An MSc in Mathematics Yeshiva University New York -2017-2019

Skills

- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills.
- Strong problem-solving skills.
- Ability to explain complex mathematical concepts simply.
- Advanced knowledge in calculus, algebra, and statistics.

Achievements

100% result throughout the teaching career.

Students enjoy learning with me.